{
    "id": "87c2b4935d6b43e2ae9f70e64b8523fd",
    "title": "Phrasal Verbs With Go",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "7b47a00d97644d619ba9076a7b3b6de2",
            "title": "Phrasal Verbs With Go",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Gambling goes ........................... my principles.",
                    "description": "If something goes against your principles, you cannot agree with that. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "out",
                        "in",
                        "against"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "She has gone ...................... a lot of hardships.",
                    "description": "To go through something is to experience it. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "with",
                        "out",
                        "for",
                        "through"
                    ],
                    "correct": 3
                },
                {
                    "question": "I will go ...................... these files if I get time.",
                    "description": "To go through something is to examine it carefully. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "in",
                        "for",
                        "across",
                        "through"
                    ],
                    "correct": 3
                },
                {
                    "question": "Whether you give us your support or not we will go ......................",
                    "description": "To go ahead is to proceed. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "along",
                        "ahead",
                        "about"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I think I am going ...................... with flu.",
                    "description": "To go down with flu is to become ill with it. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "in",
                        "down",
                        "on",
                        "ahead"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Have we got enough food to go .....................?",
                    "description": "Go round  = have enough to serve everybody around",
                    "answers": [
                        "round",
                        "over",
                        "on"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "We have gone a bit too far. Don't you think we should go ................... now?",
                    "description": "To go back is to return to a previous position. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "down",
                        "back",
                        "in"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Although I hadn't provoked the dog, he went ....................... me.",
                    "description": "To go for somebody is to attack them. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "on",
                        "for",
                        "with"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Don't forget to go ......................... your notes before exam.",
                    "description": "To go over notes is to revise them. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "over",
                        "after",
                        "on"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Prices of essential commodities have gone .........................",
                    "description": "When prices go up, they increase. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "through",
                        "up",
                        "over"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He went ........................ his family business as soon as he had completed his MBA.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "for",
                        "into",
                        "at"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "James is going ......................... with a French girl.",
                    "description": "To go out with somebody is to have a romantic relationship with them. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "on",
                        "after",
                        "out"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}